A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants E-G FA732C FA732C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - E to G
  - Federal University of Bahia (08550065), 1984 September 01-1984 November 30 (Reel 5056;5531)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE ELEVENTH BRAZILIAN CONGRESS ON HUMAN REPRODUCTION, TO BE HELD IN SAO PAULO, SEPTEMBER 1984
    Burns, Kathryn J.
  - Federal University of Bahia (08851054), 1988 September 01-1992 December 31 (Reel 6311;6543)
    SUPPORT FOR UNIVERSITY RESEARCH AND TRAINING IN AFRO-BRAZILIAN STUDIES
    Smith, Bradford
  - Federal University of Bahia (08950854), 1989 July 01-1992 December 31 (Reel 6307;6550)
    SUPPORT FOR ACTION RESEARCH AND TECNHICAL ASSISTANCE TO DISADVATANGED WOMEN'S GROUPS IN THE STATE OF BAHIA
  - Federal University of Bahia (09100195), 1990 December 01-1993 March 31 (Reel 6323;6532)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND EDUCATION ON RACE AND GENDER DISCRIMINATION IN THE LABOR MARKET
  - Federal University of Bahia (09200364), 1992 January 01-1995 December 31 (Reel 7074)
    SUPPORT FOR AFRICAN BRAZILIAN STUDIES AND TRAINING
    Alvarez, Sonia E.;Brooke, Nigel P.
    Brazil; Blacks -- Brazil -- Study and teaching; Federal University of Bahia
  - Federal University of Bahia (09251076), 1992 July 01-1994 July 01 (Reel 6702;6848)
    SUPPORT FOR SUPPLEMENTAL TRAINING AND A REGIONAL NETWORK OF WOMEN'S STUDIES SCHOLARS IN THE NORTH AND NORTHEAST OF BRAZIL
  - Federal University of Bahia (09300917), 1993 May 01-1995 October 31 (Reel 7007;7228)
    Brazil; Women--Employment--Brazil--Salvador (Brazil); Federal University of Bahia
  - Federal University of Bahia (09501215), 1995 August 01-1999 December 31 (Reel 8267)
    RESEARCH AND TRAINING IN PARTICIPATORY SCHOOL MANAGEMENT
    $282,000.00;$282,000.00
  - Federal University of Bahia (09501217), 1995 August 01-1998 August 31 (Reel 7872)
    NON-FORMAL TECHNICAL TRAINING FOR AFRICAN BRAZILIANS
  - Federal University of Bahia (09501218), 1995 August 01-2001 December 31 (Reel 8818)
    RESEARCH PROGRAM ON ANTI-RACIST EDUCATION AND JUDICIAL REFORM
    $340,000.00;$340,000.00
  - Federal University of Bahia (09900199), 1998 October 01-2000 November 30 (Reel 8770)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH, TRAINING AND OUTREACH IN PARTICIPATORY SCHOOL MANAGEMENT
    Brazil; Education -- Aims and objectives -- Brazil; School management and organization--Brazil; Federal University of Bahia
  - Federal University of Bahia (09900873), 1999 March 01-2005 February 28 (Reel 9153)
    RACE-RELATED SUPPLEMENTARY EDUCATION AND CURRICULUM DEVELOPMENT AND PUBLIC DEBATE ON AFFIRMATIVE ACTION
    $347,000.00;$347,000.00
    Brazil; Affirmative action programs -- Brazil; Women--Health and hygiene--Brazil; Curriculum planning -- Brazil; Federal University of Bahia
  - Federal University of Bahia (09901033), 1999 May 01-2001 December 31 (Reel 8889)
    SUPPORT FOR MULTI-DISCIPLINARY RESEARCH ON REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH
    Brazil; Women--Health and hygiene--Research--Brazil; Sexual health -- Research -- Brazil; Interdisciplinary research -- Health and hygiene -- Brazil; Federal University of Bahia
  - Federal University of Bahia (09901377), 1999 August 01-2003 August 31 (Reel 9153)
    Support for a multicenter study on adolescent pregnancy and reproductive health in three Brazilian cities
    $301,100.00;$301,100.00
    Brazil; Teenage girls--Health and hygiene--Brazil; Teenage pregnancy--Brazil; Federal University of Bahia
  - Federal University of Bahia (10250434), 2001 December 01-2002 November 30 (Reel 8971)
    For technical assistance to municipal governments for the development of educational planning
    Brazil; Education -- Aims and objectives; Educational equalization -- Brazil; Federal University of Bahia
  - Federal University of Bahia (10251253), 2002 May 01-2004 April 30 (Reel 9100)
    For the Center for Afro and Afro-Oriental Studies to develop a training program on ethnic and race relations for African-Brazilian undergraduate and graduate students
    Dora, Denise Dourado;Leal, Ondina Fachel
  - Federal University of Bahia (10350454), 2003 February 01-2005 January 31 (Reel 9102)
  - Federal University of Bahia (10350509), 2002 July 01-2003 June 30 (Reel 9068)
    For the National Federation of Business Administration Students' awards program to encourage social responsibility among its membership
    $30,000.00;$18,579.70
  - Federal University of Ceara (06400407), 1964 July 09-1981 December 31 (Reel 3637;3638;4451;4462;5991)
    STRENGTHENING OF ECONOMICS TEACHING AND RESEARCH IN NORTHEAST BRAZIL
    $692,000.00;$692,000.00
    Brazil; Federal University of Ceara
  - Federal University of Ceara (06900731), 1969 October 09-1980 August 25 (Reel 3119;3120;3560)
    DEVELOPMENT OF GRADUATE TRAINING AND RESEARCH IN AGRICULTURAL ECONOMICS IN BRAZIL'S NORTHEAST
    $422,320.00;$422,320.00
  - Federal University of Ceara (07000520), 1970 August 04-1980 December 31 (Reel 2820;3843)
    RESEARCH AND TRAINING IN SORGHUM PRODUCTION
    $219,000.00;$219,000.00
  - Federal University of Ceara (07200244), 1972 July 18-1978 July 18 (Reel 2729;3278;3279)
    EDUCATIONAL RESEARCH PROGRAM IN THE FACULTY OF EDUCATION
    $82,000.00;$78,011.92
  - Federal University of Ceara (07400637), 1974 November 01-1978 October 05 (Reel 2798;3280)
    FAMILY PLANNING IN MATERNAL AND CHILD HEALTH SERVICES IN BRAZIL
  - Federal University of Ceara (08250392), 1982 January 06-1986 September 30 (Reel 5345;5560)
    SUPPORT OF THE MASTER'S PROGRAM IN ECONOMICS AT THE UNIVERSITY OF CEARA
  - Federal University of Ceara (08700271), 1987 January 01-1990 January 01 (Reel 6087)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND TRAINING IN REGIONAL RESOURCE ECONOMICS (BRAZIL)
    $140,915.00;$140,915.00
    May, Peter H.;Anderson, Anthony B. (Anthony Bennett)
  - Federal University of Ceara (08950408), 1989 March 01-1990 March 31 (Reel 6100)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR AN INTENSIVE TRAINING COURSE IN NATURAL RESOURCE AND ENVIRONMENTAL IMPACT ASSESSMENT
    $13,110.00;$13,014.98
  - Federal University of Ceara (10051805), 2000 August 01-2003 February 28 (Reel 8949)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY TO EVALUATE CHANGES IN PUBLIC SECURITY POLICY IN THE NORTHEASTERN STATE OF CEARA
    Brazil; Community policing -- Brazil; Federal University of Ceara
  - Federal University of Juiz De Fora (07100432), 1971 July 14-1979 May 23 (Reel 2803;3276;3277;4103)
    DEVELOPMENT OF RESEARCH AND TEACHING IN REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY
    Perkin, Gordon W.;Schuman, Barry K.
    Brazil; Federal University of Juiz De Fora
  - Federal University of Juiz De Fora (10251086), 2002 June 01-2004 May 31 (Reel 9246)
    For the Center for Public Education Policy and Evaluation to conduct a comprehensive education and administration program to improve municipal school management
    Brazil; Education -- Aims and objectives -- Brazil; School management and organization--Brazil; Federal University of Juiz De Fora
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (06600115), 1966 February 02-1984 December 31 (Reel 4478;4489;5205;5227;5229;5919)
    DEVELOPMENT OF TEACHING AND RESEARCH IN POLITICAL SCIENCE AT THE UNIVERSITY IN BRAZIL
    $864,000.00;$864,000.00
    Sanderson, Steven E.
    Brazil; Federal University of Minas Gerais
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (06800879), 1968 September 27-1980 December 31 (Reel 3707;3755;4553)
    STRENGTHENING THE UNIVERSITY'S CENTER FOR REGIONAL DEVELOPMENT AND PLANNING
    $686,600.00;$686,600.00
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (07400557), 1977 October 17-1987 December 31 (Reel 5505)
    PROGRAM OF SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH AND TRAINING IN THE FIELD OF EDUCATION
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (07600537), 1976 September 16-1977 September 15 (Reel 1285;3282)
    SUPPORT FOR A COLLABORATIVE STUDY OF BRAZIL'S 1976 MUNICIPIAL ELECTIONS
    Himes, James R.
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (07800888), 1978 October 30-1982 April 30 (Reel 3087;3563;4275)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH, TRAINING AND INTERCHANGE ON THE DEVELOPMENT OF THE AMAZON
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (07850596), 1978 June 13-1983 June 13 (Reel 4265;5509)
    SUPPORT TO ENABLE THE DEPARTMENT OF POLITICAL SCIENCE TO PURCHASE BOOKS AND RENEW PERIODICAL SUBSCRIPTIONS ABROAD
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (08950227), 1988 October 01-1989 September 30 (Reel 5915)
    SUPPORT FOR A REFERENCE SERVICE ON AMAZON POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT
    $28,800.00;$28,800.00
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (09050755), 1990 January 01-1991 December 31 (Reel 6113)
    SUPPORT AN ACADEMIC SEMINAR ON DEMOGRAPHIC INDICATORS OF RACIAL INEQUALITY IN BRAZIL
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (09351330), 1993 August 01-1994 December 31 (Reel 7051)
    RESEARCH INVESTIGATING TELEVISION'S INFLUENCE ON RAPID FERTILITY DECLINE IN BRAZIL
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (09901543), 1999 August 01-2001 July 31 (Reel 8613)
    SUPPORT FOR A POLICE/UNIVERSITY PARTNERSHIP TO CREATE A CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF CRIMINOLOGY AND PUBLIC SECURITY
    Brazil (Rio de Janeiro);Mexico and Central America (Mexico City)
    Brown, Kimberli R.;Leeds, Elizabeth R.
    Brazil; Criminal Justice, Administration of -- Study and teaching -- Brazil; Federal University of Minas Gerais
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (10051147), 2000 May 01-2001 July 31 (Reel 8664)
    SUPPORT FOR A SYMPOSIUM TO PLAN THE IMPLEMENTATION OF REGULAR HOUSEHOLD SURVEYS IN BELO HORIZONTE, BRAZIL, FOR GUIDING METROPOLITAN AREA SOCIAL POLICY
    Brazil; Policy sciences; Household surveys -- Brazil -- Congresses; Federal University of Minas Gerais
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (10100737), 2001 April 01-2003 March 31 (Reel 8983)
    Support for a training program on research and data management on race/ethnicity and reproductive health indicators
    Brazil; Blacks -- Brazil -- Social conditions -- Research; Sexual health -- Brazil -- Research; Race Discrimination--Brazil--Research; Federal University of Minas Gerais
  - Federal University of Minas Gerais (10150370), 2000 December 01-2002 June 30 (Reel 9013)
    Support for a study on the institutional potential of replicating the innovative Brazilian experience of participatory budgeting
    Brazil; Budget -- Brazil -- Citizen participation -- Research; Municipal government--Finance--Brazil--Citizen participation; Fiscal policy -- Brazil; Federal University of Minas Gerais
  - Federal University of Para (07300514), 1973 June 27-1979 September 01 (Reel 3612;3680;5530;7248)
    SUPPORT FOR TRAINING, DOCUMENTATION AND RESEARCH AT THE "NUCLEO DE ALTOS ESTUDOS AMAZONICOS"
    Brazil; Federal University of Para
  - Federal University of Para (07800889), 1978 October 30-1981 April 30 (Reel 3090;4275)
  - Federal University of Para (08950190), 1989 February 01-1991 October 30 (Reel 6101)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND DOCUMENTATION OF IMPACTS OF MINING INDUSTRIES IN EASTERN AMAZON ON THE REGION'S POOR
    $33,700.00;$33,700.00
  - Federal University of Para (09251199), 1992 September 01-1993 March 01 (Reel 6765;7226)
    SUPPORT FOR PLANNING AN AMAZON-BASED DOCTORAL PROGRAM IN ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT IN THE HUMID TROPICS
    Anderson, Anthony B. (Anthony Bennett);Dassin, Joan
    Brazil; Latin America; Federal University of Para
  - Federal University of Para (09300525), 1993 April 01-1995 August 31 (Reel 7187;7487)
    CONSOLIDATION OF A RESEARCH AND TRAINING PROGRAM IN SMALL-SCALE FARMING SYSTEMS
    $66,000.00;$65,475.92
  - Federal University of Para (09450878), 1994 August 01-1996 July 31 (Reel 7110;7595)
    DEVELOPMENT OF TIDE-GENERATED ELECTRIC ENERGY FOR USE BY RURAL INHABITANTS IN THE AMAZON DELTA
  - Federal University of Para (09600486), 1996 May 01-2002 December 31 (Reel 9008)
    $107,500.00;$107,500.00
  - Federal University of Para (09701245), 1997 August 01-2000 July 31 (Reel 9045)
    RESEARCH, POLICY REVIEW, AND COMMUNICATIONS ON SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT AND LOCAL GOVERNANCE IN THE AMAZON
    $180,000.00;$180,000.00
  - Federal University of Para (09901726), 2000 January 01-2002 December 31 (Reel 8968)
    APPLIED RESEARCH, PUBLIC FORA AND DISSEMINATION ON SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT AND LOCAL GOVERNANCE IN THE EASTERN AMAZON
    $210,000.00;$209,747.65
    Brazil; Sustainable development--Brazil; Environmental policy -- Brazil; Conservation of natural resources -- Amazon River Region; Federal University of Para
  - Federal University of Parana (06600193), 1966 April 28-1971 April 27 (Reel 1822;1823)
    TEACHER-TRAINING PROGRAM IN VOCATIONAL-AGRICULTURAL EDUCATION IN BRAZIL
    $1,100,000.00;$366,646.91
    Brazil; Federal University of Parana
  - Federal University of Parana (10350906), 2003 April 01-2004 March 31 (Reel 9068)
    To evaluate the Federal Fluminense University's year-long course for mid-career officials of the Military Police of Rio de Janeiro
    $15,500.00;$15,500.00
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (06400485), 1964 September 22-1968 September 21 (Reel 2169;3107)
    ESTABLISHMENT OF A SCIENCE TEACHING CENTER IN NORTHEAST BRAZIL
    Rao, K. N.
    Brazil; Federal University of Pernambuco
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (07000138), 1970 February 27-1984 July 11 (Reel 5389;5490;5498;5886)
    DEVELOPMENT OF GRADUATE TRAINING AND RESEARCH IN SOCIOLOGY AND ECONOMICS
    $647,000.00;$647,000.00
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (07100328), 1971 May 24-1979 February 07 (Reel 2791)
    STRENGTHENING APPLIED RESEARCH ON NUTRITION IN THE BRAZILIAN NORTHEAST
    $227,500.00;$227,500.00
    Hakim, Peter;Hertford, Reed
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (07650208), 1975 December 12-1976 December 11 (Reel 3367;4274)
    SUPPORT OF A MASTER OF SCIENCE PROGRAM IN COGNITIVE PSYCHOLOGY AT THE UNIVERSITY
    $4,142.00;$4,142.00
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (07850642), 1978 April 04-1978 August 03 (Reel 2877)
    SUPPORT FOR SERVICES OF A VISITING PROFESSOR TO THE DEPARTMENT OF NUTRITION OF THE UNIVERSITY
    $2,095.00;$2,095.00
    Gardner, James A.;Hakim, Peter;Hertford, Reed
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (07950754), 1979 August 08-1984 December 31 (Reel 5545)
    SUPPORT FOR A MULTIDISCIPLINARY RESEARCH PROJECT ON MALNUTRITION IN THE "AGRESTE" RURAL AREA OF PERNAMBUCO
    $85,209.00;$85,209.00
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (08050453), 1980 March 06-1980 June 05 (Reel 2974)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A SEMINAR ON "NEW ALTERNATIVES FOR THE HEALTH SECTOR"
    $662.00;$662.00
    Gardner, James A.
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (08100395), 1981 April 22-1983 April 21 (Reel 4261;5512)
    ASSESSMENT OF DIFFERENTIAL AGRICULTURAL POLICY IMPACT ON SMALL FARMERS IN PERNAMBUCO, BRAZIL
    $76,800.00;$76,800.00
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (08350228), 1982 November 22-1983 May 21 (Reel 4843;5557)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT POLICY IN THE STATE OF PERNAMBUCO, BRAZIL
    $4,880.00;$4,880.00
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (08350946), 1983 August 12-1984 February 11 (Reel 4251;5542)
    SUPPORT FOR AN INTERNSHIP PROGRAM OF HEALTH CARE AND HEALTH EDUCA-TION IN POOR COMMUNITIES OF METROPOLITAN RECIFE, BRAZIL
    $3,743.00;$3,743.00
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (08801146), 1988 September 01-1994 December 31 (Reel 6702;6919)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON BENEFITS AND COSTS OF BRAZILIAN PROTECTION OF ITS MICROCOMPUTER INDUSTRY
    $58,000.00;$57,989.77
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (08850118), 1987 September 01-1988 August 31 (Reel 5748;5759)
    SUPPORT FOR THE STUDY OF HOUSEHOLDS, GENDER AND PUBLIC POLICIES
  - Federal University of Pernambuco (10100681), 2001 April 01-2003 March 31 (Reel 9151)
    Applied research and community outreach, and public education on sexuality and reproductive rights
    Brazil; Sexual health -- Brazil -- Information services; Women's rights--Brazil; Federal University of Pernambuco
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (06100367), 1961 September 27-1965 July 15 (Reel 0720;3100)
    ESTABLISHMENT OF A COMMITTEE FOR GRADUATE STUDIES
    Federal University of Rio De Janeiro
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (06200393), 1962 July 18-1965 July 17 (Reel 0722;3102)
    DEVELOPMENT OF POSTGRADUATE TEACHING AND RESEARCH IN THE BASIC SCIENCES
    $650,000.00;$640,867.09
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (06700103), 1967 January 19-1969 January 18 (Reel 1853;3116)
    PLANNING AND CURRICULUM DEVELOPMENT FOR THE FACULTY OF EDUCATION
    $102,000.00;$59,054.10
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (06700450), 1967 July 25-1973 March 19 (Reel 4471;4472;5205;5250;5539;5540)
    CENTER FOR GRADUATE STUDY IN LINGUISTICS
    $557,600.00;$557,600.00
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (06700464), 1967 August 04-1972 April 13 (Reel 1865;3276)
    REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY RESEARCH
    $254,000.00;$254,000.00
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (06800479), 1968 June 12-1978 March 08 (Reel 2686;2687;4471;5539)
    DEVELOPMENT OF GRADUATE TEACHING AND RESEARCH IN SOCIAL ANTHROPOLOGY
    $569,000.00;$569,000.00
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (06900101), 1968 December 13-1973 December 31 (Reel 1576;3118)
    STRENGTHENING GRADUATE TRAINING AND RESEARCH PROGRAMS IN THE BASIC SCIENCES
    $231,000.00;$219,693.04
    Silva, Alberto Carvalho da;Rao, K. N.
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (07700620), 1977 September 02-1980 April 30 (Reel 3013;3282)
    SUPPORT FOR GRADUATE TRAINING AND RESEARCH IN SOCIAL ANTHROPOLOGY
    $76,000.00;$75,980.92
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (07750013), 1976 September 15-1978 January 31 (Reel 2858;3282)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT TO THE GRADUATE PROGRAM IN SOCIAL ANTHROPOLOGY OF THE DEPARTMENT OF ANTHROPOLOGY OF THE NATIONAL MUSEUM
    Gardner, James A.;Himes, James R.
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (08050296), 1979 December 11-1982 September 30 (Reel 4262;5506)
    SUPPORT FOR LIBRARY ACQUISITIONS FOR THE GRADUATE PROGRAM OF SOCIAL ANTHROPOLOGY AT THE NATIONAL MUSEUM
    $15,000.00;$14,960.38
    Brazil; Federal University of Rio De Janeiro
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (08350923), 1983 August 03-1987 September 30 (Reel 5253;5542)
    SUPPORT FOR THE ACQUISITION OF FOREIGN LIBRARY MATERIALS FOR THE GRADUATE PROGRAM IN SOCIAL ANTHROPOLOGY (BRAZIL)
    $15,652.00;$15,652.00
    Fry, Peter
  - Federal University of Rio de Janeiro (08400709), 1984 September 19-1993 October 31 (Reel 6459;6546)
    SUPPORT FOR THE GRADUATE PROGRAM IN SOCIAL ANTHROPOLOGY AT THE NATIONAL MUSEUM
    $680,000.00;$680,000.00
    Dassin, Joan;Smith, Bradford
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (08450418), 1984 January 01-1985 April 30 (Reel 4473;5542)
    SUPPORT FOR THE GRADUATE PROGRAM IN SOCIAL ANTHROPOLOGY AT THE NATIONAL MUSEUM (BRAZIL)
  - Federal University of Rio de Janeiro (08700430), 1987 May 01-1993 June 30 (Reel 6698;6919)
    SUPPORT FOR A NATIONAL SURVEY OF INDIAN LANDS IN BRAZIL AND ASSOCIATED RESEARCH
    $257,500.00;$257,500.00
    May, Peter H.;Anderson, Anthony B. (Anthony Bennett);Smith, Bradford
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (08800514), 1988 March 01-1991 January 31 (Reel 6087)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND TRAINING IN ENERGY ECONOMICS AND POLICY AND ON THE SOCIAL IMPACTS OF MAJOR HYDROELECTRIC PROJECTS
    $249,200.00;$248,955.41
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (08801145), 1988 September 01-1990 November 30 (Reel 5748;5922)
    SUPPORT FOR COMPARATIVE RESEARCH ON INDUSTRIAL GROWTH STRATEGIES IN BRAZIL, ASIA AND EUROPE
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (08950278), 1989 January 01-1989 July 01 (Reel 5929)
    SUPPORT FOR A DIAGNOSIS OF TRIBAL HEALTH CONDITIONS TO TRAIN INDIGENOUS MEDICAL PROMOTERS
    $5,800.00;$5,788.93
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (09050939), 1990 June 01-1993 February 28 (Reel 6497;6532)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AMD AN ACADEMIC SEMINAR ON FEMALE HOME BASED WORKERS IN RIO DE JANEIRO
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (09250164), 1991 October 01-1994 May 31 (Reel 6701;6848)
    SUPPORT TO COMPLETE AN ANALYSIS OF THE SOCIAL, ENVIRONMENTAL AND POLICY IMPLICATIONS OF LARGE-SCALE HYDROELECTRIC DAMS IN BRAZIL
    $49,800.00;$49,800.00
    Anderson, Anthony B. (Anthony Bennett);Dassin, Joan;Smith, Bradford
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (09400566), 1994 February 01-1999 December 31 (Reel 8345)
    SUPERVISION OF MOZAMBICAN SOCIAL SCIENCE UNDERGRADUATES AND DEVELOPING MOZAMBICAN STUDIES IN BRAZIL
    Brazil (Rio de Janeiro);Eastern Africa (Nairobi)
    Brooke, Nigel P.;Wilson, Kenneth
    Brazil; Mozambique; Federal University of Rio De Janeiro
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (09451169), 1994 August 01-1998 July 31 (Reel 7732)
    TIE-OFF SUPPORT FOR ACQUISITION OF LIBRARY MATERIALS
    $20,000.00;$19,994.38
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (09800186), 1997 October 01-2000 November 30 (Reel 8747)
    RESEARCH AND PUBLIC FORA ON ENVIRONMENTAL MANAGEMENT, GOVERNANCE AND CIVIC PARTICIPATION ISSUES IN BRAZIL
    Leeds, Elizabeth R.;Lopez, Jose Gabriel
    Brazil; Sustainable development--Brazil; Environmental policy -- Brazil; Federal University of Rio De Janeiro
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (09850731), 1998 May 01-2000 March 31 (Reel 8314)
    APPLIED RESEARCH, PUBLIC FORA, AND PUBLICATIONS ON INDIGENOUS RIGHTS, GOVERNANCE AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT ISSUES
    Brazil; Sustainable development--Brazil; Indians of South America -- Brazil; Land tenure--Brazil; Human rights -- Brazil; Federal University of Rio De Janeiro
  - Federal University of Rio De Janeiro (09900205), 1999 January 01-2002 January 31 (Reel 8955)
    APPLIED RESEARCH & PUBLIC FORA ON POVERTY& SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENTIN BRAZIL'S NORTHEAST REGION
    $135,000.00;$134,998.35
    Brazil; Sustainable development--Brazil; Federal University of Rio De Janeiro
  - Federal University of Rio de Janeiro (10000385), 2000 May 01-2004 November 30 (Reel 9120)
    SUPPORT FOR COUNTRY-WIDE COMPARATIVE RESEARCH ON POPULAR PARTICIPATION IN MUNICIPAL ADMINISTRATION IN BRAZIL
    $150,000.00;$149,956.96
    Leeds, Elizabeth R.;Toni, Ana
    Brazil; Government -- Citizen participation -- Brazil; Federal University of Rio De Janeiro
  - Federal University of Rio de Janeiro (10001328), 2000 July 01-2003 June 30 (Reel 8970)
    RESEARCH, PUBLIC FORA, AND TRAINING ON INDIGENOUS RIGHTS, GOVERNANCE, AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT ISSUES
    $325,000.00;$325,000.00
    Brazil; Sustainable development--Brazil--Research; Indigenous peoples -- Brazil -- Legal status, laws etc.; Indians of South America -- Legal status, laws etc.p; Federal University of Rio De Janeiro
  - Federal University of Rio de Janeiro (10151880), 2001 August 01-2003 January 31 (Reel 9021)
    For a multimedia museum exhibition on the history, peoples and culture of a land reform process in northeastern Brazil
    Brazil; Land reform--Brazil; Federal University of Rio De Janeiro
  - Federal University of Rio de Janeiro (10351380), 2003 July 01-2004 June 30 (Reel 9151)
    For research and public forums on land reform settlements, social movements and sustainable development in the northeastern state of Pernambuco
  - Federal University of Rio Grande Do Norte (08350415), 1983 April 11-1987 March 30 (Reel 5306)
    SUPPORT FOR A TRAINING PROGRAM IN THE ARTS FOR CHILDREN AND ADOLESCENTS IN TWO LOW-INCOME NEIGHBORHOODS IN NATAL (BRAZIL)
    $36,000.00;$36,000.00
    Brazil; Federal University of Rio Grande Do Norte
  - Federal University Of Rio Grande Do Sul (06100198), 1961 May 23-1966 May 22 (Reel 0720;3100)
    IMPROVEMENT OF THE UNDERGRADUATE ECONOMICS PROGRAM
    Manitzas, Nita R.
    Federal University Of Rio Grande Do Sul
  - Federal University Of Rio Grande Do Sul (06700102), 1967 January 18-1975 December 31 (Reel 2819;2820;3116;3807)
    DEVELOPMENT OF POLITICAL AND ADMINISTRATIVE STUDIES
    $443,000.00;$443,000.00
    Schuman, Barry K.
    Brazil; Federal University Of Rio Grande Do Sul
  - Federal University Of Rio Grande Do Sul (07000025), 1969 October 17-1980 October 08 (Reel 2508;2509;3122;3793)
    STRENGTHENING OF GRADUATE TRAINING AND RESEARCH IN THE RURAL SOCIAL SCIENCES